Boston School of Occupational Therapy (BSOT) Records UA032
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Student records, 1918 -- 2012; 1918 -- 2009; UA032.002; 38.9 Linear Feet
  - Gordon, Ruth Ellen, 1972 -- 1976; UA032.002.119.00003 (Box 119)
  - Gordon, Stacey, 1995 -- 1997; UA032.002.119.00004 (Box 119)
  - Gordon, Taber, 1995 -- 2000; UA032.002.119.00005 (Box 119)
  - Gorton, Gail, 1973 -- 1981; UA032.002.119.00006 (Box 119)
  - Goshgarian, Barbara L., 1963 -- 1965; UA032.002.119.00007 (Box 119)
  - Gott, Judith Anne, 1965 -- 1966; UA032.002.119.00008 (Box 119)
  - Piner, Juliet Anne (Gottlieb), 1955 -- 1960; UA032.002.119.00009 (Box 119)
  - Graham, Jennifer, 1995 -- 1997; UA032.002.119.00010 (Box 119)
  - DeMelle, Jennifer (Grant), 1992 -- 1993; UA032.002.119.00011 (Box 119)
  - Gray, Carol Ann, 1971 -- 1974; UA032.002.119.00012 (Box 119)
  - Grayston, Maria, 2005; UA032.002.119.00013 (Box 119)
  - Greeley, Deborah Marie, 1971 -- 1973; UA032.002.119.00014 (Box 119)
  - Green, Dennis, 1994 -- 1996; UA032.002.119.00015 (Box 119)
  - Greenberg, Ilana, 2000 -- 2002; UA032.002.119.00016 (Box 119)
  - Greene, Joanne, 1995 -- 1997; UA032.002.119.00017 (Box 119)
  - Gefter, Sharon Wilma (Greene), 1962 -- 1966; UA032.002.119.00018 (Box 119)
  - Greenbaum, Sarah A., 1985 -- 1987; UA032.002.119.00019 (Box 119)
  - Greenhalgh, Ellen, 1990 -- 1996; UA032.002.119.00020 (Box 119)
  - Greenway, Virginia, 1975 -- 1979; UA032.002.119.00021 (Box 119)
  - Greeno, Sharon L., 1978 -- 1981; UA032.002.119.00022 (Box 119)
  - Vander May, Linda Lea (Gregg), 1964 -- 1967; UA032.002.119.00023 (Box 119)
  - Gresh, Bruce, 1974 -- 1976; UA032.002.119.00024 (Box 119)
  - Gribbons, Nicole, 2000 -- 2002; UA032.002.119.00025 (Box 119)
  - Griggs, Caroline White, 2000 -- 2002; UA032.002.119.00026 (Box 119)
  - Grimm, Rebecca, 1999 -- 2001; UA032.002.119.00027 (Box 119)
  - Grodin, Mary Ellen, 1967 -- 1971; UA032.002.119.00028 (Box 119)
  - Gross, Allison, 1997 -- 1999; UA032.002.119.00029 (Box 119)
  - Snider, Elizabeth Anne (Gross), 1966 -- 1970; UA032.002.119.00030 (Box 119)
  - Gross, Margo Ruth, 1969 -- 1971; UA032.002.119.00031 (Box 119)
  - Grosz, Ingrid L., 1998 -- 2000; UA032.002.119.00032 (Box 119)
  - Grygiel, Anne, 2001 -- 2003; UA032.002.119.00033 (Box 119)
  - Guertin, Laura, 1994 -- 1996; UA032.002.119.00034 (Box 119)
  - Guess, Jennifer, 2005; UA032.002.119.00035 (Box 119)
  - Gugnani, Meeta, 1996 -- 1999; UA032.002.119.00036 (Box 119)
  - Gulbas, Ruth, 1986 -- 1990; UA032.002.119.00037 (Box 119)
  - Gustafson, Marc J., 2002; UA032.002.119.00038 (Box 119)
  - Gutman, Jill, 1977 -- 1981; UA032.002.119.00039 (Box 119)
  - Guttman. Judy ann, 1956 -- 1958; UA032.002.119.00040 (Box 119)
  - Guzik, Joan, 1975 -- 1980; UA032.002.119.00041 (Box 119)
  - Gyba, susan, 1975 -- 1980; UA032.002.119.00042 (Box 119)
  - Fiorentino, Paula Marie (Habecker), 1966 -- 1970; UA032.002.119.00043 (Box 119)
  - Hack, Joanne sue, 1970 -- 1976; UA032.002.119.00044 (Box 119)
  - Hackett, Elizabeth, 1986; UA032.002.119.00045 (Box 119)
  - Haines, Liv, 1998 -- 2000; UA032.002.119.00046 (Box 119)
  - Hall, Diane Marie, 1994 -- 1996; UA032.002.119.00047 (Box 119)
  - Hall, Stacy K., 1976 -- 1981; UA032.002.119.00048 (Box 119)
  - Haller, Kathleen A., 1982 -- 1987; UA032.002.119.00049 (Box 119)
  - Halliday, Karen, 1987 -- 1989; UA032.002.119.00050 (Box 119)
  - Halliday, Tracy M., 1998 -- 2000; UA032.002.119.00051 (Box 119)
  - Halpenny, Claire, 2007; UA032.002.119.00052 (Box 119)
  - Halpern, Susan, 1994 -- 1996; UA032.002.119.00053 (Box 119)
  - Halpin, Bridget, 2006; UA032.002.119.00054 (Box 119)
  - Halunen, Gretchen, 1993 -- 1995; UA032.002.119.00055 (Box 119)
  - Hamerling, Marlene, 1964 -- 1968; UA032.002.119.00056 (Box 119)
  - Hamilton, Ellyn L., 1963 -- 1965; UA032.002.119.00057 (Box 119)
  - Hamilton, Jennifer, 1993 -- 1995; UA032.002.119.00058 (Box 119)
  - Hamilton, Sarah E., 1984 -- 1988; UA032.002.119.00059 (Box 119)
  - Hamilton, Susannah, 1996 -- 1998; UA032.002.119.00060 (Box 119)
  - Hamm, Amanda, 2005; UA032.002.119.00061 (Box 119)
  - Hammoud, Farah, 1994 -- 2000; UA032.002.119.00062 (Box 119)
  - Hampton, Annabel, 2004 -- 2005; UA032.002.119.00063 (Box 119)
  - Hand, Deborah, 1987 -- 1991; UA032.002.119.00064 (Box 119)
  - Handler, Deborah, 1986 -- 1988; UA032.002.119.00065 (Box 119)
  - Handler, Martha, 1973 -- 1978; UA032.002.119.00066 (Box 119)
  - Hanlon, Susan, 1991 -- 1993; UA032.002.119.00067 (Box 119)
  - Hanna, Michele L., 1978 -- 1985; UA032.002.119.00068 (Box 119)
  - Hanna, Toni R., 1977 -- 1981; UA032.002.119.00069 (Box 119)
  - Hannigan, Kerry, 1998 -- 2001; UA032.002.119.00070 (Box 119)
  - Hansend, Holly A., 1982 -- 1986; UA032.002.119.00071 (Box 119)
  - Hard, Cynthia Louisa, 1973 -- 1977; UA032.002.119.00072 (Box 119)
  - Harding-Morick, Emily, 1994 -- 1996; UA032.002.119.00073 (Box 119)
  - Godart, Amy e. (Harkins), 1998 -- 2000; UA032.002.119.00074 (Box 119)
  - Hatnett, Elizabeth A., 1974 -- 1977; UA032.002.119.00075 (Box 119)
  - Harnett, Sarah Ann, 1972 -- 1974; UA032.002.119.00076 (Box 119)
  - Haro, Marcela, 1990 -- 1992; UA032.002.119.00077 (Box 119)
  - Harper, Beverly, 1994 -- 1995; UA032.002.119.00078 (Box 119)
  - Harper, Deborah, 2000 -- 2002; UA032.002.119.00079 (Box 119)
  - Harper, Holliday Harrison, 1980 -- 1983; UA032.002.119.00080 (Box 119)
  - Harper, Karen L., 1975 -- 1979; UA032.002.119.00081 (Box 119)
  - Harris, Laura Faye, 1996 -- 1999; UA032.002.119.00082 (Box 119)
  - Harris, Amanda, 2004 -- 2006; UA032.002.119.00083 (Box 119)
  - Harris, Kristen, 1990 -- 1992; UA032.002.119.00084 (Box 119)
  - Harris, Kristin, 2006; UA032.002.119.00085 (Box 119)
  - Harris, Patricia M., 1976 -- 1980; UA032.002.119.00086 (Box 119)
  - Harrison, Angela M., 1973 -- 1977; UA032.002.119.00087 (Box 119)
  - Harrison, Claudia, 1970 -- 1973; UA032.002.119.00088 (Box 119)
  - Harrison, Hope, 1974 -- 1977; UA032.002.119.00089 (Box 119)
  - Harrison, Mary Ellen, 1980 -- 1984; UA032.002.119.00090 (Box 119)
  - Nichols, Nina Ward (Harrison), 1966 -- 1969; UA032.002.119.00091 (Box 119)
  - Hartman, Laura A., 1998 -- 2000; UA032.002.119.00092 (Box 119)
  - Hartwell, Cordelia Carter, 1959 -- 1962; UA032.002.119.00093 (Box 119)
  - Kolack, Lillian (hasselman), 2004 -- 2006; UA032.002.119.00094 (Box 119)
  - Hastings, Philomena M., 1977 -- 1981; UA032.002.119.00095 (Box 119)
  - Hatch, Maureen Helen, 1973 -- 1975; UA032.002.119.00096 (Box 119)
  - Hathaway, Amy, 2005; UA032.002.119.00097 (Box 119)
  - Hatherly, Kathleen, 2000 -- 2002; UA032.002.119.00098 (Box 119)
  - Hawes, Lynn, 1954 -- 1956; UA032.002.119.00099 (Box 119)
  - Hawkings, Lisa, 2003 -- 2004; UA032.002.119.00100 (Box 119)
  - Hawkings, Valerie Kay, 1973 -- 1977; UA032.002.119.00101 (Box 119)
  - Hayden, Melissa, 1998 -- 2000; UA032.002.119.00102 (Box 119)
  - Hayes, Alice Mac Arthur, 1972 -- 1974; UA032.002.119.00103 (Box 119)
  - Hayes, Cynthia, 1976 -- 1981; UA032.002.119.00104 (Box 119)
  - Hayes, Laurie, 1998 -- 2000; UA032.002.119.00105 (Box 119)
  - Hayes, Maureen E. (Haddad), 1962 -- 1966; UA032.002.119.00106 (Box 119)
  - Haynes, Tanya, 1996 -- 1998; UA032.002.119.00107 (Box 119)
  - Haynie, Deirdre, 1992 -- 1994; UA032.002.119.00108 (Box 119)
  - Hazen, Linda Ann, 1965 -- 1969; UA032.002.119.00109 (Box 119)
  - Hearne, Elizabeth Ann, 1975 -- 1979; UA032.002.119.00110 (Box 119)
  - Heartquist, Jessica, 1998 -- 2000; UA032.002.119.00111 (Box 119)
  - Hebert, Katherine, 2003 -- 2007; UA032.002.119.00112 (Box 119)
  - Heeremans, Susan, 1990 -- 1992; UA032.002.120.00001 (Box 120)
  - Heet, Corinne A., 1998 -- 1999; UA032.002.120.00002 (Box 120)
  - Hegquist, Leigh, 1996 -- 1999; UA032.002.120.00003 (Box 120)
  - Heim, Charlotte, 2001 -- 2003; UA032.002.120.00004 (Box 120)
  - Heisler, Gretchen, 1968 -- 1973; UA032.002.120.00005 (Box 120)
  - Heiss, Anne (Joseph), 1992 -- 1994; UA032.002.120.00006 (Box 120)
  - Helfand, Lois Jane, 1963; UA032.002.120.00007 (Box 120)
  - Helfen, Laurel Ann, 1973 -- 1976; UA032.002.120.00008 (Box 120)
  - Helaeson, Loriann (Gerancher), 1990 -- 1992; UA032.002.120.00009 (Box 120)
  - Helwing, Natalie, 2000 -- 2002; UA032.002.120.00010 (Box 120)
  - Hemingway, Rodney D., 1994 -- 1999; UA032.002.120.00011 (Box 120)
  - Hemingway, Rodney, 1998; UA032.002.120.00012 (Box 120)
  - Hengeveld, Tara, 1969 -- 1973; UA032.002.120.00013 (Box 120)
  - Henkind, Karen Grace, 1977 -- 1981; UA032.002.120.00014 (Box 120)
  - Hennessey, Martha Ann, 1973 -- 1976; UA032.002.120.00015 (Box 120)
  - Henry, Alexis D., 1976 -- 1980; UA032.002.120.00016 (Box 120)
  - Henry, Diana Ashby, 1973 -- 2003; UA032.002.120.00017 (Box 120)
  - Henson, Patricia T., 1981 -- 1985; UA032.002.120.00018 (Box 120)
  - Herlihy, Kathleen Ann, 1974 -- 1978; UA032.002.120.00019 (Box 120)
  - Herlihy, Lynn-Marie, 1996 -- 1998; UA032.002.120.00020 (Box 120)
  - Herr, Jo-Anne, 1993 -- 1995; UA032.002.120.00021 (Box 120)
  - Herrera, Gloria, 1993 -- 1995; UA032.002.120.00022 (Box 120)
  - Herskovitz, Sara Elaine, 1973 -- 1976; UA032.002.120.00023 (Box 120)
  - Hersum, Cynthia Stratton, 1958 -- 1963; UA032.002.120.00024 (Box 120)
  - Herzberg, Susan Barnes, 1965 -- 2000; UA032.002.120.00025 (Box 120)
  - Hesse, Jocelyn, 1990 -- 1992; UA032.002.120.00026 (Box 120)
  - Hettlinger, Karen, 1994 -- 1996; UA032.002.120.00027 (Box 120)
  - Heyman, Joanne, 1986; UA032.002.120.00028 (Box 120)
  - Hick, Kristen, 1991 -- 1994; UA032.002.120.00029 (Box 120)
  - Hickmott, Nancy Adele, 1981 -- 1985; UA032.002.120.00030 (Box 120)
  - Hickok, Elizabeth, 1998 -- 2000; UA032.002.120.00031 (Box 120)
  - Norton, Dorothy Perkins (Hill), 1958 -- 1961; UA032.002.120.00032 (Box 120)
  - Higgins, Susan M., 1982 -- 1986; UA032.002.120.00033 (Box 120)
  - Higgins, Susan, 1996 -- 2007; UA032.002.120.00034 (Box 120)
  - Hilliard, Judith A., 1985 -- 1989; UA032.002.120.00035 (Box 120)
  - Himmer, Reese, 2006 -- 2008; UA032.002.120.00036 (Box 120)
  - Hinderliter, Jennifer, 1992 -- 1994; UA032.002.120.00037 (Box 120)
  - Hirsch, Lois Hermine, 1960 -- 1964; UA032.002.120.00038 (Box 120)
  - Hirsch, Allison Ellenbogen, 2006 -- 2009; UA032.002.120.00039 (Box 120)
  - Hirsch, Susanne Gail, 1956 -- 1961; UA032.002.120.00040 (Box 120)
  - Hiserman, Ila, 2000 -- 2002; UA032.002.120.00041 (Box 120)
  - Hocky, Susan D., 1975 -- 1980; UA032.002.120.00042 (Box 120)
  - Hoelterling, Lisa A., 1986 -- 1987; UA032.002.120.00043 (Box 120)
  - Hoey, Elaine F., 1983 -- 1987; UA032.002.120.00044 (Box 120)
  - Hoffenberg, Tracey, 2007 -- 2008; UA032.002.120.00045 (Box 120)
  - Hofler, Linda, 1973 -- 1977; UA032.002.120.00046 (Box 120)
  - Hogg, Phoebe, 1977 -- 1981; UA032.002.120.00047 (Box 120)
  - Holcombe, Elizabeth Lee, 1962 -- 1963; UA032.002.120.00048 (Box 120)
  - Hollaman, Lucy, 1973 -- 1977; UA032.002.120.00049 (Box 120)
  - Holland, Linda J., 1977 -- 1981; UA032.002.120.00050 (Box 120)
  - Hollander, Laura Lee, 1974 -- 1975; UA032.002.120.00051 (Box 120)
  - Hollander, Susan Leigh, 1971 -- 1976; UA032.002.120.00052 (Box 120)
  - Holler, Dorinda, 1997 -- 1999; UA032.002.120.00053 (Box 120)
  - Holleran, Beth, 1996 -- 1998; UA032.002.120.00054 (Box 120)
  - Hollenbeck, Jan Kathryn, 1981 -- 1983; UA032.002.120.00055 (Box 120)
  - Holmes, Heidi, 1996 -- 1998; UA032.002.120.00056 (Box 120)
  - Holt, Caroline Thompson, 1969 -- 1973; UA032.002.120.00057 (Box 120)
  - Hooker, Barbara Keith, 1971 -- 1974; UA032.002.120.00058 (Box 120)
  - Woodruff, Janet M. (Hopkins), 1961 -- 1963; UA032.002.120.00059 (Box 120)
  - Hopkins, Priscilla, 1974 -- 1978; UA032.002.120.00060 (Box 120)
  - Hopkins, Susan Kay, 1975 -- 1979; UA032.002.120.00061 (Box 120)
  - Horgar, Lynn, 1993 -- 1995; UA032.002.120.00062 (Box 120)
  - Horin, Amy, 2001 -- 2003; UA032.002.120.00063 (Box 120)
  - Horst, Paul Richard, 1980 -- 1982; UA032.002.120.00064 (Box 120)
  - Hotchkiss, Tyche, 1994 -- 1996; UA032.002.120.00065 (Box 120)
  - Howard, Alison B., 1998 -- 2000; UA032.002.120.00066 (Box 120)
  - Howe, Marcella Ann, 1966 -- 1969; UA032.002.120.00067 (Box 120)
  - Hoye, Maureen, 1999 -- 2002; UA032.002.120.00068 (Box 120)
  - Hoye, Maureen, 1965 -- 1967; UA032.002.120.00069 (Box 120)
  - Hsieh, Ching-hui, 1995 -- 1996; UA032.002.120.00070 (Box 120)
  - Clemson, Christine (Hubbard), 1987 -- 1994; UA032.002.120.00071 (Box 120)
  - Hubbell, Wendy Barnes, 1969 -- 1974; UA032.002.120.00072 (Box 120)
  - Hughes, Darlene L., 1983 -- 1987; UA032.002.120.00073 (Box 120)
  - Hughes, Mary J., 1982 -- 1986; UA032.002.120.00074 (Box 120)
  - Hulbert, Nancy (Hoop), 1960 -- 1963; UA032.002.120.00075 (Box 120)
  - Hulseberg, Debra Ann, 1974 -- 1978; UA032.002.120.00076 (Box 120)
  - Hume, Ellen, 1987 -- 1990; UA032.002.120.00077 (Box 120)
  - Hung, Shan-Shan, 1984; UA032.002.120.00078 (Box 120)
  - Hunt, Carol A., 1962 -- 1965; UA032.002.120.00079 (Box 120)
  - Huntington, Sarah, 1988 -- 1991; UA032.002.120.00080 (Box 120)
  - Hyde, Elizabeth, 1977 -- 1980; UA032.002.120.00081 (Box 120)
  - Hyde, Jonathan, 1995 -- 2001; UA032.002.120.00082 (Box 120)
  - Hyman, Amy Lynn, 1974 -- 1978; UA032.002.120.00083 (Box 120)
  - Iafrate, Cynthia, 1984 -- 1989; UA032.002.120.00084 (Box 120)
  - Iani, Joan (Mathews), 2001; UA032.002.120.00085 (Box 120)
  - Iida, Cindy N., 1984 -- 1986; UA032.002.120.00086 (Box 120)
  - Ippolito, Marie, 1979 -- 1983; UA032.002.120.00087 (Box 120)
  - Irvine, Patricia Ann, 1972 -- 1975; UA032.002.120.00088 (Box 120)
  - Irvings, Lisa R., 1988 -- 1990; UA032.002.120.00089 (Box 120)
  - Irwin, Greta (Bame), 1983 -- 2009; UA032.002.120.00090 (Box 120)
  - Isidro, Amy, 1991 -- 1993; UA032.002.120.00091 (Box 120)
  - Iwo, Carolin, 2000 -- 2004; UA032.002.120.00092 (Box 120)
  - Jablonski, Debra A., 1986 -- 1990; UA032.002.120.00093 (Box 120)
  - Jackson, Beth, 1993 -- 1995; UA032.002.120.00094 (Box 120)
  - Jackson, Jane Ann, 1993 -- 1995; UA032.002.120.00095a (Box 120)
  - Jackson, Lisa, 2004 -- 2009; UA032.002.120.00095b (Box 120)
  - Jackson, Marisa C., 1986 -- 1987; UA032.002.120.00096 (Box 120)
  - Jackson, Nancy, 1999 -- 2001; UA032.002.120.00097 (Box 120)
  - Jacob, Dori, 2001 -- 2008; UA032.002.120.00098 (Box 120)
  - Bank, Laura Ellen (Jacob), 1964 -- 1968; UA032.002.120.00099 (Box 120)
  - Jacobs, Janet Martha, 1958 -- 1960; UA032.002.120.00100 (Box 120)
  - Jacobson, Annmarie, 1996 -- 1998; UA032.002.120.00101 (Box 120)
  - James, Nancy Bradley, 1973 -- 1976; UA032.002.120.00102 (Box 120)
  - Jankot, Julia, 2001 -- 2003; UA032.002.120.00103 (Box 120)
  - Jarossi, John, 1997 -- 1999; UA032.002.120.00104 (Box 120)
  - Jeffers, Doreen, 1992 -- 1994; UA032.002.120.00105 (Box 120)
  - Jennings, Kristy, 2002 -- 2007; UA032.002.120.00106 (Box 120)
  - Jennings, Phyllis Natalie (Ashwell), 1967 -- 1968; UA032.002.120.00107 (Box 120)
  - Jeng, Shu-Ywe, 1992 -- 1995; UA032.002.120.00108 (Box 120)
  - Jensen, Carol Jean Beatrice, 1967 -- 1968; UA032.002.120.00109 (Box 120)
  - Jewett, Susan Ann (Igowsky), 1970 -- 1973; UA032.002.120.00110 (Box 120)
  - Joe, Stephanie, 2004 -- 2007; UA032.002.120.00111 (Box 120)
  - Johns, Linda C., 1977 -- 1981; UA032.002.121.00001 (Box 121)
  - Johnson, Allison M., 2002 -- 2007; UA032.002.121.00002 (Box 121)
  - Johnson, Erica D., 1963 -- 1967; UA032.002.121.00003 (Box 121)
  - Johnson, Gretchen, 2003 -- 2007; UA032.002.121.00004 (Box 121)
  - Johnson, Nancy Carol, 1959 -- 1962; UA032.002.121.00005 (Box 121)
  - Johnson, SallyAnne, 2002 -- 2003; UA032.002.121.00006 (Box 121)
  - Johnson, Sharon, 2004 -- 2006; UA032.002.121.00007 (Box 121)
  - Johnston, Jan Allyn, 1975 -- 1979; UA032.002.121.00008 (Box 121)
  - Joanne, Jolly-Kay, 1984 -- 1986; UA032.002.121.00009 (Box 121)
  - Jones, Jean, 1994 -- 1996; UA032.002.121.00010 (Box 121)
  - Jones, Jo-Ellen Carletta, 1972 -- 1976; UA032.002.121.00011 (Box 121)
  - Jones, Kelly A., 1987 -- 1989; UA032.002.121.00012 (Box 121)
  - Josephs, Kristen M., 1985 -- 1991; UA032.002.121.00013 (Box 121)
  - Josephs, Kristen M., 1985 -- 1989; UA032.002.121.00014 (Box 121)
  - Judge, Camerion, 2002 -- 2007; UA032.002.121.00015 (Box 121)
  - Judge, Maria, 1969 -- 1973; UA032.002.121.00016 (Box 121)
  - Judge, Nancy Elizabeth, 1980 -- 1984; UA032.002.121.00017 (Box 121)
  - Juros, Christine L., 1986 -- 1987; UA032.002.121.00018 (Box 121)
  - Kafka, Elizabeth, 2000 -- 2002; UA032.002.121.00019 (Box 121)
  - Kahan, Robin J., 1985 -- 1989; UA032.002.121.00020 (Box 121)
  - Kahn, Marjorie, 1999 -- 2001; UA032.002.121.00021 (Box 121)
  - Kalb, Laurie Jill, 1974 -- 1999; UA032.002.121.00022 (Box 121)
  - Kallfelz, Ann Elizabeth, 1987 -- 1988; UA032.002.121.00023 (Box 121)
  - Kaltman, Ilya Ann, 1972 -- 1975; UA032.002.121.00024 (Box 121)
  - Kampner, Carol Alfonso, 1959 -- 1963; UA032.002.121.00025 (Box 121)
  - Kanarakis, Fotini, 1993 -- 1996; UA032.002.121.00026 (Box 121)
  - Kaplan, Joan Susan, 1993 -- 1996; UA032.002.121.00027 (Box 121)
  - Kartin, Naomi Judith, 1973 -- 1977; UA032.002.121.00028 (Box 121)
  - Courteol, Mary Melinda (Kasch), 1967 -- 1970; UA032.002.121.00029 (Box 121)
  - Kasten, Audrey J., 1976 -- 1981; UA032.002.121.00030 (Box 121)
  - Kasten, Ilana, 2001 -- 2003; UA032.002.121.00031 (Box 121)
  - Katz, Elisa, 1994 -- 1996; UA032.002.121.00032 (Box 121)
  - Katz, Laura R., 1978 -- 1982; UA032.002.121.00033 (Box 121)
  - Katz, Nancy Joyce, 1974 -- 1977; UA032.002.121.00034 (Box 121)
  - Katzmann, Debra B., 1976 -- 1980; UA032.002.121.00035 (Box 121)
  - Kaufman, Jody B., 1976 -- 1981; UA032.002.121.00036 (Box 121)
  - Kaufman, Marsha Jay, 1968 -- 1971; UA032.002.121.00037 (Box 121)
  - Kaur, Harpreet, 2002 -- 2007; UA032.002.121.00038 (Box 121)
  - Kay, Jennie A., 2002 -- 2004; UA032.002.121.00039 (Box 121)
  - Kaye, Andrea Helen, 1964 -- 1967; UA032.002.121.00040 (Box 121)
  - Kedziorek, Regina, 1979 -- 1983; UA032.002.121.00041 (Box 121)
  - Keebler, Nancy, 1998 -- 2000; UA032.002.121.00042 (Box 121)
  - Keegan, Bernadette, 2003 -- 2007; UA032.002.121.00043 (Box 121)
  - Parker, Nancy Jean (Keegan), 1964 -- 1968; UA032.002.121.00044 (Box 121)
  - Keller, Nancy R., 1973 -- 1976; UA032.002.121.00045 (Box 121)
  - Keller, Wendy, 1992 -- 1995; UA032.002.121.00046 (Box 121)
  - Kelly, Sean, 1996 -- 1998; UA032.002.121.00047 (Box 121)
  - Kemnitz, Sharon, 1995 -- 1997; UA032.002.121.00048 (Box 121)
  - Kemp, Ann (Sayre), 1992 -- 1995; UA032.002.121.00049 (Box 121)
  - Kenneally (Sheehy), Kathleen, 1996 -- 2000; UA032.002.121.00050 (Box 121)
  - Kennedy, Donna L., 1980 -- 2000; UA032.002.121.00051 (Box 121)
  - Kennedy, Natalie, 1994 -- 1997; UA032.002.121.00052 (Box 121)
  - Kennedy, Patricia, 1991 -- 1993; UA032.002.121.00053 (Box 121)
  - Kennedy, Patricia, 2004 -- 2007; UA032.002.121.00054 (Box 121)
  - Kennedy, Patricia, 2005 -- 2006; UA032.002.121.00055 (Box 121)
  - Kenny, Jason, 1998 -- 2000; UA032.002.121.00056 (Box 121)
  - Kent, Kaitlyn Mary, 2005 -- 2008; UA032.002.121.00057 (Box 121)
  - Keogh, Kathryn, 1993 -- 1995; UA032.002.121.00058 (Box 121)
  - Kerls, Daniel R., 1998; UA032.002.121.00059 (Box 121)
  - Lidsky, Meryl Claire (Kern), 1962 -- 1965; UA032.002.121.00060 (Box 121)
  - Kessler, Beth Irene, 1972 -- 1974; UA032.002.121.00061 (Box 121)
  - Goode, Eileen Ann (Kessner), 1970 -- 1971; UA032.002.121.00062 (Box 121)
  - Kidder, Betsy, 1996 -- 1998; UA032.002.121.00063 (Box 121)
  - Kienast, Erika, 1994 -- 2000; UA032.002.121.00064 (Box 121)
  - Kilayka, Christina, 1991 -- 1993; UA032.002.121.00065 (Box 121)
  - Kilgore, Kim, 1997 -- 2000; UA032.002.121.00066 (Box 121)
  - Kilman, Marina, 1997 -- 2000; UA032.002.121.00067 (Box 121)
  - Kim, Eunice, 2003 -- 2007; UA032.002.121.00068 (Box 121)
  - Kim, Mi, 2002 -- 2004; UA032.002.121.00069 (Box 121)
  - Kimball, Cynthia, 1995 -- 1997; UA032.002.121.00070 (Box 121)
  - Kimmelman, Marilyn Irene, 1969; UA032.002.121.00071 (Box 121)
  - King, Dana, 1999 -- 2000; UA032.002.121.00072 (Box 121)
  - King, Elisabeth, 2006; UA032.002.121.00073 (Box 121)
  - Anderson, Kathryn (King), 2001 -- 2005; UA032.002.121.00074 (Box 121)
  - King, Maureen, 1991 -- 1995; UA032.002.121.00075 (Box 121)
  - Kingman, Karolyn, 1997 -- 1999; UA032.002.121.00076 (Box 121)
  - Kennealey, Moya, 1962 -- 1965; UA032.002.121.00077 (Box 121)
  - Kinsey, David R., 1998 -- 2001; UA032.002.121.00078 (Box 121)
  - Kirby, Lori A., 2000 -- 2003; UA032.002.121.00079 (Box 121)
  - Kiritsis, Katherine, 1994 -- 1996; UA032.002.121.00080 (Box 121)
  - Kish, Jacqueline, 2006 -- 2009; UA032.002.121.00081 (Box 121)
  - Kishi, Janis, 1993 -- 1995; UA032.002.121.00082 (Box 121)
  - Klein, Colleen M., 1985 -- 1991; UA032.002.121.00083 (Box 121)
  - Klein, Elaine Mae, 1973 -- 1977; UA032.002.121.00084 (Box 121)
  - Klein, Jennifer Gale, 1974 -- 1976; UA032.002.121.00085 (Box 121)
  - Klein, Jodi, 1975 -- 1980; UA032.002.121.00086 (Box 121)
  - Klein, Linda A., 1963; UA032.002.121.00087 (Box 121)
  - Klein, Willa Anne, 1958; UA032.002.121.00088 (Box 121)
  - Topperman, Marcia Sue (Kleinberg), 1967 -- 1971; UA032.002.121.00089 (Box 121)
  - Klemer, Jane, 1962 -- 1963; UA032.002.121.00090 (Box 121)
  - Cochran, Margarita Frew (Klug), 1962 -- 1963; UA032.002.121.00091 (Box 121)
  - Klug, Mary L., 1978 -- 1981; UA032.002.121.00092 (Box 121)
  - Knee, Beth E., 1979 -- 1981; UA032.002.121.00093 (Box 121)
  - Knoblock, Jan Elizabeth (Mars), 1979 -- 1981; UA032.002.121.00094a (Box 121)
  - Kodis, Rebecca, 1992 -- 1995; UA032.002.121.00094b (Box 121)
  - Koegel, Rhonda, 1992 -- 1995; UA032.002.121.00095 (Box 121)
  - Kohler, Beth Mary, 1973 -- 1977; UA032.002.121.00096 (Box 121)
  - Richards, Martha Dee (Kohlwey), 1966 -- 1970; UA032.002.121.00097 (Box 121)
  - Kolton, Sondra, 1957 -- 1959; UA032.002.121.00098 (Box 121)
  - Segal, Sharon Faye (Korchin), 1977 -- 2009; UA032.002.122.00001 (Box 122)
  - Kordova, Adina, 2002 -- 2003; UA032.002.122.00002 (Box 122)
  - Korwan, Anne M., 1998 -- 2000; UA032.002.122.00003 (Box 122)
  - Koutras, Nicole, 2000 -- 2002; UA032.002.122.00004 (Box 122)
  - Santelli, Jean Marie (Kouwe), 1971 -- 1973; UA032.002.122.00005 (Box 122)
  - Kovar, Holly-Jean, 1967 -- 1971; UA032.002.122.00006 (Box 122)
  - Koveleski, Jennifer, 1994 -- 1996; UA032.002.122.00007 (Box 122)
  - Krasnoff, Cheryl, 1999 -- 2001; UA032.002.122.00008 (Box 122)
  - Kratchman, Madalyn H., 1974 -- 1977; UA032.002.122.00009 (Box 122)
  - Krause, Kathryne J., 1974 -- 1981; UA032.002.122.00010 (Box 122)
  - Krawiec, Catherine Marie, 1975 -- 1979; UA032.002.122.00011 (Box 122)
  - Krebs, Lawrence J., 1988 -- 1990; UA032.002.122.00012 (Box 122)
  - Krebs, Victoria, 2002 -- 2007; UA032.002.122.00013 (Box 122)
  - Kreilkamp, Rosamond, 1974 -- 1976; UA032.002.122.00014 (Box 122)
  - Kreisberg, Amy Lynn, 1976 -- 1980; UA032.002.122.00015 (Box 122)
  - Platt, Barbara (Kresge), 1989 -- 1991; UA032.002.122.00016 (Box 122)
  - Krouse. Debra Lynn, 1974 -- 1977; UA032.002.122.00017 (Box 122)
  - Krudysz, Jane, 1987 -- 1989; UA032.002.122.00018 (Box 122)
  - Krug, Marie annette, 1985 -- 1990; UA032.002.122.00019 (Box 122)
  - Steinglass, Rochelle (Kruger), 1958 -- 1963; UA032.002.122.00020 (Box 121)
  - Kryzhevsky, Irma, 1994 -- 1996; UA032.002.122.00022 (Box 122)
  - Kuklinski, Judith Mary Anne, 1973 -- 1975; UA032.002.122.00023 (Box 122)
  - Kulenkamplemmers, Felicitas, 1982 -- 1985; UA032.002.122.00024 (Box 122)
  - Kunstaetter, Daisy (Isacovicci), 1985 -- 1986; UA032.002.122.00025 (Box 122)
  - Kuntz, Nancy M., 1983 -- 1987; UA032.002.122.00026 (Box 122)
  - Kupferman, Danielle, 1999 -- 2001; UA032.002.122.00027 (Box 122)
  - Kurtz, Pamela, 1998 -- 1999; UA032.002.122.00028 (Box 122)
  - Kypar, Irene, 1991 -- 1994; UA032.002.122.00029 (Box 122)
  - La Cour, Karen, 1989 -- 1990; UA032.002.122.00030 (Box 122)
  - Laclair, Wendy, 1999 -- 2001; UA032.002.122.00031 (Box 122)
  - Ladd, Melissa, 1999 -- 2001; UA032.002.122.00032 (Box 122)
  - Zager, Amy I. (Ladestsky), 1998 -- 2000; UA032.002.122.00033 (Box 122)
  - Laiter, Lisa Pauling, 1975 -- 1979; UA032.002.122.00034 (Box 122)